Guide to the Douglas Killgore video materials, 1911-2013 UA 405
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Media
  - Rice Diploma Prep and Interview, Registrar's Office, (DV), 2005-05-13 (Box 3)
  - Strassman and Queller interviews, Project LEARN, (DV), 2005-06-16 (Box 3)
  - Rudy Guerra interview, Project LEARN, (DV), 2005-06-22 (Box 3)
  - Rick Smalley interview in Rice lab for Project Learn (3), (DVD), 2005-06-23 (Box 3)
  - Richard Smalley interview, Project LEARN, (DV), 2005-06-23 (Box 3)
  - Mission Continues; Small is Big, Rice Media, (DVD), 2005-06-29 (Box 4)
  - David Leebron / Call to Conversation #1 of 2, (DV), 2005-07 (Box 3)
  - David Leebron / Call to Conversation #2 of 2, (DV), 2005-07 (Box 3)
  - Mary McHale / Guinness Nanotube interview, (DV), 2005-07-11 (Box 3)
  - Ferrari Nano Lecture Camera 1, (DV), 2005-07-27 (Box 3)
  - Ferrari Nano Lecture Camera 2, (DV), 2005-07-27 (Box 3)
  - David Leebron matriculation, (DV), 2005-08 (Box 3)
  - Tony Gorry / Educating the Net Generation (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2005-08-18 (Box 4)
  - Anthony Gorry / Teaching the Net Generation, (DV), 2005-08-18 (Box 3)
  - Engineering Students; Dean of Engineering Admission #1 of 2, (DV), 2005-08-20 (Box 3)
  - Engineering Students; Dean of Engineering Admission #2 of 2, (DV), 2005-08-20 (Box 3)
  - Leebron, Boles, Call to Conversation Cam 1, (DV), 2005-08-26 (Box 3)
  - Leebron, Boles, Call to Conversation Cam 2, (DV), 2005-08-26 (Box 3)
  - New Professor Lecture Series, (DV), 2005-08-30 (Box 3)
  - Meffert, (DV), 2005-09 (Box 3)
  - Rice DMS: Lisa Spiro Lunch, (DV), 2005-09-14 (Box 3)
  - Feniosky Pena-Mora / Dynamic Planning and Control of Civil Infrastructure Systems, Rice IT, (DVD), 2005-09-19 (Box 3)
  - Hurricane Katrina and Houston, Rice IT, (DVD), 2005-09-21 (Box 4)
  - Rice DMS: Hurricane, (DV), 2005-09-21 (Box 3)
  - El Dia, Part 1, Hamman Hall, (DV), 2005-09-28 (Box 3)
  - El Dia, Part 2, Hamman Hall, (DV), 2005-09-28 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Interviews: Barbara McKittrick, Kraettli Epperson, Alex Byrd, Allan Van Fleet, Rice IT, (DVD), 2005-09-29 (Box 4)
  - Jose Ignacio Cabrujas / El Dia Que Me Quieras (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2005-09-29 (Box 4)
  - Alumni Panel, (DV), 2005-09-30 (Box 3)
  - Dr. John Boles: David Leebron, A Short History of Rice University (6), Rice Media Services, (DVD), 2005-10 (Box 4)
  - DOC class, student intros, (DV), 2005-10 (Box 3)
  - Rice DMS: Project Grad 1, (DV), 2005-10-03 (Box 3)
  - Richard B. Alley / How to Get Rich and Save the World (2), Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2005-10-06 (Box 4)
  - Rachel Tobias memorial service, (DV), 2005-10-12 (Box 3)
  - Robert Pinsky / The American Town: Dreams and Nightmares, Part 1, Rice Media, (DVD), 2005-10-18 (Box 4)
  - Robert Pinsky, Part 1, (DV), 2005-10-18 (Box 3)
  - Robert Pinsky, Part 2, (DV), 2005-10-20 (Box 3)
  - Poet Laureate [Robert Pinsky], Part 3, (DV), 2005-10-20 (Box 3)
  - Ping Sun lunch lecture, no sound, (DV), 2005-10-25 (Box 3)
  - Project Grad 2, (DV), 2005-10-27 (Box 3)
  - Data Backup: Smalley clips for Doc. Talk from Nano, Guinness at computer, Small, Curl and Kroto receiving Nobel Prize, Rice Media, (DVD), 2005-10-28 (Box 3)
  - Celebrating the Life of Richard E. Smalley, (DVD), 2005-11-02 (Box 4)
  - Global E and C Forum #4, (DVD), 2005-11-05 (Box 3)
  - Ping Sun Lecture Series, (DV), 2005-11-14 (Box 3)
  - Robots ELEC, (DV), 2005-11-18 (Box 3)
  - Richard Tapia / Successes and Challenges in Diversifying, Rice IT, (DVD), 2005-11-29 (Box 4)
  - Project Grad narration, part 1, (DV), 2005-12 (Box 3)
  - Project Grad Kettleton School, Doug Cam, (DV), 2005-12 (Box 3)
  - Y. Ping Sun, Chinese Delegation Meeting, Rice Media, (DVD), 2005-12-02 (Box 4)
  - Leebron signing agreement with Chinese officials #1, (DV), 2005-12-02 (Box 3)
  - Leebron signing agreement with Chinese officials #2, (DV), 2005-12-02 (Box 3)
  - Ping Sun interviews 05? 06?, Rice Media, (DVD), 2005-2006 (Box 3)
  - Rice Energy Symposium, Redo, (DV), 2006 (Box 5)
  - Time Travel, Documentary Seminar Production [class taught by Doug Killgore], (DVD), 2006 (Box 3)
  - Secretary of Rice Alumni Assn., (DV), 2006 (Box 3)
  - Boles, (DV), 2006 (Box 3)
  - Sustainable Show Tape, (DV), 2006 (Box 3)
  - Richard Smalley memorial #2, (DV), 2006 (Box 5)
  - Air Car and Beyond the Fringe, (DVD), 2006-01-01 (Box 5)
  - Robin Forman, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-01-06 (Box 5)
  - Nano lunch, (DV), 2006-01-09 (Box 5)
  - Rice Energy Summit #3, (DVD), 2006-01-10 (Box 3)
  - Rice Energy Symposium, #4 unedited, Rice, (DVD), 2006-01-10 (Box 3)
  - Project Grad, (DVD), 2006-01-11 (Box 5)
  - Kortum class, (DV), 2006-01-11 (Box 5)
  - Kortum class, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-01-11 (Box 5)
  - Nano Continuing Studies lunch #2, (DV), 2006-01-12 (Box 5)
  - Nano Continuing Studies lunch #3, (DV), 2006-01-13 (Box 5)
  - Thomas R. Cole / Aging and the Changing Nature of the Human, Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2006-01-16 (Box 3)
  - Janet Rarick Internet Class, 2 of 2, (DV), 2006-01-17 (Box 5)
  - Kortum class, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-01-18 (Box 5)
  - Kortum class, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-01-18 (Box 5)
  - Paul Silverstein / Antisemitism and Islamophobia: Lessons from France, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-01-20 (Box 3)
  - Nano Forum, tape 1, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 4)
  - Nano Forum HD, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 5)
  - Nano Forum HD, Tape 3, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 5)
  - Nano Forum HD, #2, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 5)
  - Arab World, History, Cam 1, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 5)
  - Arab World, History, Cam 2, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 5)
  - Nano Forum, Day 1, (DV), 2006-01-20 (Box 5)
  - Pulickel M. Ajayan / Controlled Assembly of Carbon Nanotube Architectures, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-01-23 (Box 3)
  - Ping Sun luncheon lecture, 1 of 2, (DV), 2006-01-24 (Box 3)
  - Leebron lecture, C2C, 1 of 2, (DV), 2006-01-24 (Box 5)
  - Leebron lecture, C2C, 2 of 2, (DV), 2006-01-24 (Box 5)
  - Sallie Keller-McNulty /Reliability Reloaded, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-01-31 (Box 3)
  - Rice exterior scenes, (DV), 2006-02-02 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Xue, MEMS lecture, (DV), 2006-02-10 (Box 5)
  - Randi Martin, Psychology, (DV), 2006-02-14 (Box 3)
  - Jim Pomerantz, Cognitive, (DV), 2006-02-24 (Box 3)
  - Michael Emerson, CORRUL Project, (DV), 2006-02-24 (Box 3)
  - Bat Boy: The Musical, Sid Rich, 1 of 2, (DV), 2006-02-25 (Box 5)
  - Bat Boy: The Musical, Sid Rich, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-02-25 (Box 5)
  - Eric Schlosser / Fast Food Nation, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-02-27 (Box 3)
  - Darcy Burgund, (DV), 2006-02-27 (Box 3)
  - Ilan Pappe / The Peace Charade in Palestine and Israel, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-02-28 (Box 3)
  - Ping Sun Lecture Series, (DV), 2006-03-01 (Box 5)
  - Ideas to Action; Wine and Beer Lecture, 1 of 2, (DV), 2006-03-01 (Box 5)
  - Ideas to Action; Wine and Beer Lecture, 2 of 2, (DV), 2006-03-01 (Box 5)
  - George Lykotrafitis / Experimental Study of Dynamic Frictional Sliding Modes Along Incoherent Interfaces, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-03-02 (Box 3)
  - Cognitive - Tony Ro and Jim D., (DV), 2006-03-02 (Box 5)
  - Lykotrafitis / MEMS lecture, (DV), 2006-03-02 (Box 5)
  - Denise Chen, Cognitive R., (DV), 2006-03-02 (Box 3)
  - Teng Li / MEMS lecture, 1 of 2, (DV), 2006-03-06 (Box 5)
  - Teng Li / MEMS lecture, 2 of 2, (DV), 2006-03-06 (Box 5)
  - Teng Li / Macrp/Nano Mechanics of Flexible Macroelectronics, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-03-06 (Box 3)
  - Project Grad #15, (DV), 2006-03-10 (Box 3)
  - Wilcrest Church, (DV), 2006-03-19 (Box 3)
  - Richard E. Smalley: Celebrating an Extraordinary Life, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-03-21 (Box 3)
  - Nancy Lin, Cognitive, Burgund Lab, (DV), 2006-03-25 (Box 3)
  - CORRUL Holly Heard, (DV), 2006-03-27 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Donor Luncheon, Student Scholar, (DV), 2006-03-28 (Box 5)
  - Computer Science Meeting #1, (DV), 2006-03-29 (Box 3)
  - Stephen Klineberg, (DV), 2006-03-30 (Box 3)
  - Elizabeth Long, CORRUL, (DV), 2006-03-30 (Box 3)
  - Richard Smalley memorial #1, (DV), 2006-03-31 (Box 5)
  - Michael Emerson / Ping Sun Lecture, (DV), 2006-04-04 (Box 3)
  - USA Immigration: Truths and Myths, Part 2, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-04-09 (Box 3)
  - Mira Nair / Between Two Worlds (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-04-11 (Box 3)
  - Statue Vid Party Round Table -- HDV ORIG, (DV), 2006-04-11 (Box 6)
  - Turner Whitted / Procedural Graphics: Trends and Challenges, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-04-13 (Box 3)
  - McNair Hall renaming -- incomplete, power went off, (DV), 2006-04-17 (Box 3)
  - Richard Tapia in tree, (DVD) 2006-04/2006-05 (Box 3)
  - Walter Kohn / Theory of Van der Walls Interactions in the Spirit of Maxwell's Equations, Rice, (DVD), 2006-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Walter Kohn Adams, (DV), 2006-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Partnerships for Mathematics and Science, Part 1, Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2006-05-03 (Box 3)
  - Partnerships for Mathematics and Science, Part 2, Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2006-05-03 (Box 3)
  - Alumni Honors Dinner (2), Killgore, (DVD), 2006-05-13 (Box 3)
  - Jill Carroll, Boniuk, (DV), 2006-05-29 (Box 5)
  - Podcast Tag, (DV), 2006-06-08 (Box 3)
  - Foster Wheeler, Jones School, 1 PAL duplicate, (DV), 2006-06-09 (Box 3)
  - Foster Wheeler, Jones School, 2 PAL duplicate, (DV), 2006-06-09 (Box 3)
  - Foster Wheeler, Jones School, Cam 1 NTSC, (DV), 2006-06-09 (Box 3)
  - Foster Wheeler, Jones School, Cam 2 NTSC, (DV), 2006-06-09 (Box 3)
  - Bobby May interview (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-07-12 (Box 5)
  - Bobby May interview, (DV), 2006-07-12 (Box 5)
  - Terry interview, Ed Tech Project, (DV), 2006-07-18 (Box 3)
  - Derek Raybuck interview, Ed Tech Project, (DV), 2006-07-18 (Box 3)
  - Sewall Hall construction, Ed Tech Project, (DV), 2006-07-18 (Box 3)
  - Dennis Huston class, Ed Tech Project, (DV), 2006-07-18 (Box 3)
  - Grigsby G Test DVD (2), Rice IT, Killgore Studios, (DVD), 2006-08-09 (Box 1)
  - Connexions, Cam 1, (DV), 2006-08-18 (Box 5)
  - Connexions, Cam 2, (DV), 2006-08-18 (Box 5)
  - Dr. King, Connextions 3, (DV), 2006-08-21 (Box 5)
  - Lovell A. Jones / Overview of Biological Factors, Session 2, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-08-26 (Box 5)
  - Kortum, African Dr., (DV), 2006-09-01 (Box 5)
  - SOROS, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-09-08 (Box 5)
  - SOROS, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-09-08 (Box 5)
  - Richard Smalley / The Mission Continues, Rice Media, (DVD), 2006-09-09 (Box 3)
  - ACS Day 1, Tape 1, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-10 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 1, Tape 2, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-10 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 1, Tape 3, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-10 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 1, Tape 4, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-10 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 1, Tape 5, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-10 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 1, Tape 6, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-10 (Box 5)
  - Vision of Richard E. Smalley, American Chemical Society; Wade Adams, (DVD) 2006-09-10/2006-09-13 (Box 3)
  - Be a Scientist, Save the World / Wade Adams (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2006-09-11 (Box 3)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 3, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 4, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 6 [no Tape 5], (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 7, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 8, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 2, Tape 9, (DV), 2006-09-11 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 1, End of Day 2, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 3, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 4, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 5, Nano, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 6, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3, Tape 7, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS Day 3/ Final Tape, (DV), 2006-09-12 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Wade, Day 4, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Arepulli, Day 4, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Day 4, Tape 3, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Day 4, Tape 4, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Farmer, Irwin, Day 4, Tape 5, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Nuckolis, Weisman, Day 4, Tape 6, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Liu, Rizler, Day 4, Tape 7, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - ACS, Kono, Wade, Day 4, Tape 8, (DV), 2006-09-13 (Box 5)
  - O'Connor House Opening Ceremony (2), Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2006-09-15 (Box 3)
  - O'Connor House #4, (DV), 2006-09-15 (Box 3)
  - Froggy Wins, (DV), 2006-09-23 (Box 5)
  - Froggy Williams / The History of Rice Football Through the 1930s, Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2006-09-24 (Box 3)
  - Rice Stock Footage, (DVD), 2006-09-26 (Box 3)
  - Leebron / State of the University, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-09-26 (Box 3)
  - O'Connor House, (DV), 2006-09-26 (Box 5)
  - Rice Works, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-09-29 (Box 5)
  - Rice Works, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-09-29 (Box 5)
  - Misc. Campus Shots, NTSC, (DV), 2006-10 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk - Townsend #1, (DV), 2006-10-01 (Box 3)
  - Boniuk - Townsend #2, (DV), 2006-10-01 (Box 3)
  - Edward Djerejian / The Situation in the Middle East (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-10-02 (Box 3)
  - ECE Affiliates Meeting, Webcast, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-10-04 (Box 3)
  - Misc. Campus shots NTSC - RMC, etc, (DV), 2006-10-06 (Box 5)
  - Ping Campus Shots, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-10-06 (Box 5)
  - Ping Sun, US Commerce Dept. promo, (DV), 2006-10-06 (Box 5)
  - Ping Sun China Project, Ping Quote?, (DV), 2006-10-09 (Box 3)
  - Ping Sun China Project, Version of tape sent to China, (DV), 2006-10-09 (Box 3)
  - Edgar Odell Lovett by John B. Boles (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-10-12 (Box 3)
  - Promise of Tomorrow: Jack Kilby and Richard Smalley, Living History Producers, (DVD), 2006-10-12 (Box 5)
  - Rice 30-second spot, not final, (DV), 2006-10-12 (Box 5)
  - ECE, S-1, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE, S-2, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE, L-1, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE, L-2, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE Rixner, S-3, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE Rixner, L-3, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE, S-4, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - ECE, L-4, (DV), 2006-10-15 (Box 3)
  - Harry Lewis, Priscilla Huston Project, (DV), 2006-10-21 (Box 5)
  - Sports panel tape, Shell Auditorium, (DV), 2006-10-23 (Box 3)
  - Ha Jin / The Spokesman and the Tribe, Part 1, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-10-24 (Box 3)
  - Ha Jin, Campbell Lecture Series, Day 1, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-10-24 (Box 5)
  - Ha Jin, Campbell Lecture Series, Day 1, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-10-24 (Box 5)
  - Ha Jin / An Individual's Homeland, Part 3 (2), Rice Media, (DVD) 2006-10-24/2006-10-26 (Box 3)
  - HUMA Tape 1, (DV), 2006-10-25 (Box 5)
  - HUMA Tape 2 (2), (DV), 2006-10-25 (Box 5)
  - Campbell [Lecture Series], HUMA, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-10-26 (Box 5)
  - Campbell [Lecture Series], HUMA, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-10-26 (Box 5)
  - John Boles / E. O. Lovett, (DV), 2006-10-28 (Box 5)
  - Sally Ride at Rice, (DV), 2006-10-28 (Box 5)
  - President's House - Boles on Lovett, (DV), 2006-10-28 (Box 3)
  - Anthony Shadid, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-11-07 (Box 5)
  - Richard Baraniuk at President's House, (DV), 2006-11-08 (Box 5)
  - Rich Baraniuk / Connextions Update (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-11-09 (Box 3)
  - Boniuk, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-11-09 (Box 5)
  - RHS Religion, (DV), 2006-11-09 (Box 5)
  - Remembering Joe Davis (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-11-10 (Box 5)
  - Froggy Wins, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-11-10 (Box 5)
  - High Rise, 30-second spot, (DV), 2006-11-12 (Box 5)
  - Baker College masters, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-11-12 (Box 5)
  - Baker College masters, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-11-12 (Box 5)
  - Marcia O'Malley / Extending the Human Being via Robotics, (DVD), 2006-11-14 (Box 3)
  - Michael Lindsey, (DV), 2006-11-14 (Box 5)
  - Michael Lindsay, (DV), 2006-11-14 (Box 5)
  - Seymour Hersch / Chaim of Command: The Road from 9/11 to Abu Ghrab, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-11-15 (Box 5)
  - O'Malley, Byrne, Cohn / Extending the Human Being via Robotics, Rice Media, (DVD), 2006-11-24 (Box 5)
  - CRC Symposium Panelists, Rice Media, (DVD), 2006-11-28 (Box 5)
  - Michael Lindsay CORRUL video, (DVD), 2006-11-29 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-11-29 (Box 5)
  - God and We the People / William Martin (2), Boniuk Center, (DVD), 2006-11-30 (Box 5)
  - William Martin, Boniuk, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-11-30 (Box 5)
  - Karin Broker / An Artist Constructs the Human or How I See Your DNA (2), Rice Digital Media, (DVD), 2006-12-05 (Box 3)
  - Robin Forman, Ask the Expert, LEARN, (DV), 2006-12-06 (Box 5)
  - Ethics Panel TCU, (DV), 2006-12-07 (Box 5)
  - 30-second spot, Tape 1, (DV), 2006-12-12 (Box 5)
  - 30-second spot, Tape 2, (DV), 2006-12-12 (Box 5)
  - Rice 30 Second Spot, (DV), 2006-12-16 (Box 5)
  - Student Quotes, (DV), 2006-12-17 (Box 5)
  - Dina R. Khoury / Understanding the Sunni-Shi'I Divide in Iraq, Rice IT, (DVD), 2006-12-19 (Box 3)
  - Rice Scenes, (DV), 2006-12-23 (Box 3)
  - 2006 Miscellaneous Ed Tech, David Del P setting up in Sewall classroom, Rice Media, (DV), 2006-2008 (Box 3)
  - Rice Science Students in Vomit Comet, (DVD), 2007 (Box 5)
  - Rice 30-second spot, (DV), 2007 (Box 5)
  - Spanish Lab in a Backpack, (DV), 2007 (Box 5)
  - Data Backup: Gillis Testimonial, Harvey Vid, Kennedy at Rice, McMurtry College Groundbreaking, NanoGuin [Guinness], Rice Media, (DVD), 2007 (Box 5)
  - Backpack Spanish insert, (DV), 2007 (Box 5)
  - Kortum class, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-01-11 (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Richards-Kortum / Intro to Global Health Issues, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-01-11 (Box 5)
  - [William] Lawson, Boniuk, (DV), 2007-01-11 (Box 5)
  - Patsy Cooper / Making Choices: Early Literacy Learning and the Craft of Teaching, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-01-13 (Box 5)
  - Christopher Seaver / HYDRIL, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-01-23 (Box 5)
  - Patricia Crone / Tolerance in Islam (2), Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-01-23 (Box 5)
  - Jill Foote, Jones School, (DV), 2007-01-23 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-01-23 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-01-23 (Box 5)
  - Kortum, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-01-30 (Box 5)
  - An Ounce of Prevention Keeps the Germs Away, (DVD), 2007-01-31 (Box 5)
  - Karen Ostherr / Role of Media, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-02-06 (Box 5)
  - Carol Quillen, Boniuk, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-02-07 (Box 5)
  - Boniuk, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-02-07 (Box 5)
  - Patti Brock / Medical Bridges, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-02-08 (Box 5)
  - David Dow / God and We the People, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-02-08 (Box 5)
  - Dow, Boniuk, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-02-08 (Box 5)
  - David Dow, (DV), 2007-02-08 (Box 5)
  - Jill Foote #1, (DV), 2007-02-12 (Box 5)
  - Rebecca Richards-Kortum / Student Project Reports, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-02-13 (Box 5)
  - Milton Boniuk, Boniuk Center Document, (DV), 2007-02-14 (Box 5)
  - Robert Curl / Hitching a Ride on a Comet... Working with Rick Smalley, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-02-23 (Box 5)
  - Gerald R. Dickens, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-02-24 (Box 5)
  - Jerry Dennis, MATS, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-02-24 (Box 5)
  - Jerry Dennis MATS #2, (DV), 2007-02-24 (Box 5)
  - BioE260 Intro to Global Health Issues, Rice Media, (DVD) 2007-03-01/2007-03-15 (Box 5)
  - Lynne J. Brindley / The Incredible Journey: Building Great Libraries for the Digital Age (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-03-05 (Box 5)
  - Marcia O'Malley / Extending the Human Being via Robotics, (DV), 2007-03-07 (Box 5)
  - Carol Quillen, (DV), 2007-03-08 (Box 5)
  - Smalley lecture, Wade [Adams], (DV), 2007-03-11 (Box 5)
  - Peter Varman, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-03-14 (Box 5)
  - Arab Art, (DV), 2007-03-14 (Box 5)
  - Malcolm Gillis, (DV), 2007-03-14 (Box 5)
  - Carol Quillen / Democracy and Difference: Religious Pluralism in Contemporary America, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-03-15 (Box 5)
  - MEMS HSEH #1, (DV), 2007-03-15 (Box 5)
  - MEMS seminar, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-03-15 (Box 5)
  - Carol Quillen #1, (DV), 2007-03-15 (Box 5)
  - Carol Quillen #2, (DV), 2007-03-15 (Box 5)
  - Andrew J. Dick / Non-linear Phenomena in Microscale Systems, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-03-19 (Box 5)
  - Burrus, Martin, McMurtry, Nolen, Wischmeyer / College System Tomorrow, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-03-22 (Box 5)
  - Paul Reinhardt, (DV), 2007-03-23 (Box 5)
  - Alan Bowling / Agility and Dynamic Performance of Multi-Legged Robots, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-03-24 (Box 5)
  - Remarks to the Chinese Delegation / James A. Baker III, (DVD), 2007-03-26 (Box 5)
  - Remarks to the Chinese Delegation / Edward P. Djerejian, (DVD), 2007-03-27 (Box 5)
  - John Sealy Brown / Gaming and Immersive Environments Bringing Education Along, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-03-27 (Box 5)
  - Baraniuk, Casserly, Atkins, Sealy, Hammond / Review of the OER Movement, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-03-27 (Box 5)
  - Hewlett, Connexions, O'Connor House, (DV), 2007-03-27 (Box 5)
  - Hewlett, Connexions, Fondren, (DV), 2007-03-27 (Box 5)
  - Kortum, BIOE 250, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-03-27 (Box 5)
  - BIOE 301, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-03-28 (Box 5)
  - Michael Emerson / Rise of Fundamentalism, Rice, (DVD), 2007-03-29 (Box 5)
  - MEMS seminar, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-03-29 (Box 5)
  - MEMS seminar, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-03-29 (Box 5)
  - Michael Emerson #2, (DV), 2007-03-29 (Box 5)
  - The College System Tomorrow, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-03-30 (Box 5)
  - Carl Wischmeyer / The First Master of Baker College Remembers (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-03-31 (Box 5)
  - Neil Havens, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-03-31 (Box 5)
  - Neil Havens, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-03-31 (Box 5)
  - Carl Wischmeyer, (DV), 2007-03-31 (Box 5)
  - Neil Havens / History of Theater at Rice, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-04 (Box 5)
  - Lego Lab, (DV), 2007-04 (Box 5)
  - Vomit Comet prep, (DV), 2007-04-02 (Box 5)
  - Vomit Comet, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-04-02 (Box 5)
  - Dr. Bill [Wilson], (DV), 2007-04-02 (Box 5)
  - Nano Lab, (DV), 2007-04-03 (Box 5)
  - Olson Pres, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-04-03 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Workshop--Castillo-Chavez, Tapia, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-04-05 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Workshop Discussions and Wrap-up, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-04-05 (Box 5)
  - Lloyd Pate / Case Study: Unsuccessful Design, (DVD), 2007-04-10 (Box 5)
  - Recent grads interviews; Shawn Hutchins Project, (DV), 2007-04-11 (Box 5)
  - Robert Curl / Brief History of Carbon (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-04-15 (Box 5)
  - Robert Curl, Lake Canyon, Tape 1, (DV), 2007-04-15 (Box 5)
  - Jim Tour, (DV), 2007-04-17 (Box 5)
  - Vicki Colvin QandA #2, (DV), 2007-04-27 (Box 5)
  - Performing Arts Medicine Day #3: Psychological Challenges of Perforing Artists, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-04-28 (Box 5)
  - Performing Arts Medicine Day #4: Care of the Professional Voice, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-04-28 (Box 5)
  - Performing Arts Medicine Day #4: Repetitive Stress Injury and Neurology of Piano Playing, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-04-28 (Box 5)
  - Performing Arts Medicine Day #2: Hearing Disorders and Protective Devices, Rice It, (DVD), 2007-04-28 (Box 5)
  - Volunteers, (DV), 2007-04-28 (Box 5)
  - [illegible], (DV), 2007-04-28 (Box 5)
  - Dalai Lama / Meaning of Compassion in Everyday Life (2), (DVD), 2007-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Dalai Lama/Tolerance and Universal Responsibility (3), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Dalai Lama, Tape 4, (DV), 2007-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Dalai Lama #1, (DV), 2007-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Dalai Lama #2, (DV), 2007-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Dalai Lama #3, (DV), 2007-05-01 (Box 5)
  - Who Knew? Rice Pres Tape 1, (DV), 2007-05-02 (Box 5)
  - Linda Thrane et al. / Defining Rice, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-05-03 (Box 5)
  - Data Backup: Defining Rice, Olson (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-05-03 (Box 5)
  - Hellums/Akers interview; Shawn Hutchins Project, (DV), 2007-05-03 (Box 5)
  - Interview: Rice students going to Africa, (DV), 2007-05-03 (Box 5)
  - Rice Honors Dinner (2), Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-05-12 (Box 5)
  - Multiplicity: Developments and Current Issues; Charles Lewis, Helmut Finner, Ajit C. Tamhane, Rice IT, (DVD), 2007-05-17 (Box 5)
  - Willem van Zwet / Lehmann Symposium, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-05-19 (Box 5)
  - Jami McKey / Capstone Course, (DV), 2007-05-24 (Box 5)
  - Jami McKey / Capstone Course, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-05-24 (Box 5)
  - Data disk: Shepherd School Symphony, Electron Microscope and Nanolab, Exterior University Quadrangle, Rice Media, (DVD), 2007-06-06 (Box 5)
  - KPFT Boniuk Center, (DV), 2007-06-08 (Box 5)
  - BIOE 301, Tape 2, (DV), 2007-06-28 (Box 5)
  - BIOE 301, Tape 3, (DV), 2007-06-28 (Box 5)